<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>World News &#8211; Qa Developer Basf</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/world-news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 15:18:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/live-favicon.jpg</url>
	<title>World News &#8211; Qa Developer Basf</title>
	<link></link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>A Drone’s View Behind Russian Lines Cratered Fields and Charred Armor</title>
		<link>/a-drones-view-behind-russian-lines-cratered-fields-and-charred-armor/</link>
					<comments>/a-drones-view-behind-russian-lines-cratered-fields-and-charred-armor/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 15:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[World News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cratered Fields and Charred Armor]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=113</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The images a reconnaissance drone sent back to Ukrainian forces provided a vivid portrait of the Russian side of the war zone. Damaged houses gave way to cratered fields on Ukraine’s southern steppe. There was burned-out armor in a scorched...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">The images a reconnaissance drone sent back to Ukrainian forces provided a vivid portrait of the Russian side of the war zone. Damaged houses gave way to cratered fields on Ukraine’s southern steppe. There was burned-out armor in a scorched forest. A jagged Russian trench along a tree line had been blasted by American-supplied cluster munitions barely a week earlier, according to Lt. Ashot Arutiunian, the commander of the unit that recorded the images.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">He pointed to holes in the roofs of several large agricultural buildings in a village and said they had most likely been hit by the American-made HIMARS rocket system; it is known for its accuracy, and there was no damage to surrounding buildings or to a nearby church. This was on a recent morning, with Ukrainian artillery firing relentlessly, the deep rumbling explosions of the impact resonating in the distance. Mixed in were the louder explosions of Russian shells landing on Ukrainian positions.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">But Lieutenant Arutiunian was focused on the skies above. Drones have become a mainstay used by both Russian and Ukrainian forces, reconnoitering the battlefield and directing fire against enemy targets. Lieutenant Arutiunian, who uses the military call sign Doc — a reference to the doctorate in data mining he holds from Kyiv Polytechnic — commands four teams in the unmanned aerial vehicle service of the Ukrainian Volunteer Army, operating on the southern front. They deploy a variety of propeller-driven drones and planes to track Russian forces for the Ukrainian military and are constantly adjusting tactics and equipment to evade Russian interceptors.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">This week, one of the units allowed a team of New York Times journalists to accompany it on a mission close to the front line as it sent a drone into Russian-occupied territory to surveil the battlefront. A condition was that the unit’s precise location could not be reported. Amid a background of artillery fire, the team got to work under cover of a small copse of trees, unpacking equipment and setting up four antennas; those were needed to work round the threats of both Russian and Ukrainian electronic jammers that can swiftly end the flight of a drone.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">The fixed wing craft the unit’s members were using was equipped with two cameras and an independent global positioning system as backup, to give the pilot several options to bring it home should one or more of the systems fail. In this reconnaissance mission we are investigating the terrain, Lieutenant Arutiunian said. Later, back at base, they would examine the video footage on a big monitor to try to spot Russian military, he said: “We are looking for soldiers, warehouses, gasoline depots, whatever.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/a-drones-view-behind-russian-lines-cratered-fields-and-charred-armor/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
